PHAN THỊ PHƯƠNG THI

ACCOUNTING 2 YEARS EXPERIENCE



Career Objectives

As a calm person, easily adaptable to new environments, not afraid of difficulties, and like to find solutions to problems. In addition to the accounting knowledge I have learned and my passion for accounting, I want to find a suitable environment to gain more experience as well as practice my skills in handling work effectively, accurately and quickly.

Basic Information

Birthday 14/02/2001

Nationality Vietnamese

Marital status Single

Gender Female

Skills

Teamwork English

Presentation Skills Excel

Work History

Tax Accountant

True Houses Trading and Service Development Company Limited

01/2023 - 10/2024 (1 year 9 month)

- Prepare VAT declaration according to regulations.
- Collect input and output invoices and enter them into Smartpro software.
- Check and reconcile receivables and payables with customers, suppliers and internal debts.
- -Track employee advances, subcontractor payments and update costs of assigned projects.
- Compare with data on thuedientu page, contact other departments to collect invoices (if missing on email).
- Issue invoices to customers, export project inventory.
- Calculate the production cost of products.
- Process and check the reasonableness, validity and legality of invoices, avoiding incorrect information on invoices.
- Balance the balance sheet items and have a plan to handle them; avoid piling up work at the end of the year.
- Complete Financial statement for the year.
- Print all kinds of books for tax settlement and audit inspection.

Accounting Intern

S-GROVE Company Limited

10/2022 - 01/2023 (3 month)

- Support for creating shipping orders.
- Support for sales invoices.

PowerPoint Microsoft Word

Analytics

Contact Me

- ptpt0025@gmail.com
- +84-708771466
- 18/17/7D Bui The My Street, Ward 10, Tan Binh, Ho Chi Minh, Vietnam

- Support monthly inventory management and issue of warehouse receipts.
- Prepare VAT declaration according to regulations.
- Check and reconcile receivables and payables with customers, suppliers and internal debts.
- Other tasks assigned and instructed by the Chief Accountant.

Data entry clerk

World Express Company Limited

11/2021 - 11/2022 (1 year)

- Receive invoices from postmen and enter data into excel.
- Arrange invoices and documents.
- Document storage.
- Perform other tasks as required by management.

Education

Sai Gon University

Bachelors - Accounting

10/2019 - 08/2023 (3 years 10 months)

Certifications

IELTS 5.0

IDP EDUCATION

2024

Certificate in Basic Applied Information Technology

Sai Gon University

2022